## **CONTACTS**

- O Brovary, Kyiv region, Ukraine
- +38066 743-66-47
- gran777777@gmail.com
- @Maksym\_dev
- github.com/MaksymKonoplinskyi
- in linkedin.com/in/konoplinskyi/
- https://maksym.vercel.app/

## **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

## FRONT-END

## STYLES

React JS / TS

SASS

CSS<sub>3</sub>

Zustand

Tailwind

Redux

Material-UI

HTML 5
Next JS

Styled Components

Astro

WEB 3.0

Solidity

Solana

**Anchor** 

Remix

Cranq

Hardhat

# BACK-END

Node.js Nest JS

Express

Sequelize

DevOps

Docker CI/CD

Netlify

AWS

DB

PostgreSQL MongoDB Redis Tests

Unit

Integration E2E tests

Jest

Mocha

Chai

Waffle

# Maksym Konoplinskyi

Senior Fullstack WEB 3.0 Developer

#### **ABOUT MY**

Coding is my passion starting from low-level languages for programming microcontrollers to decentralized web3 applications. I have combined science, teaching, business, sports coaching, blockchain researching, due to this I received a PhD degree, published many scientific articles in international journals, professed 6000+ students, founded and successfully developed a sport club for 17 years, trained 5000+ people and sportsmen, became a successful crypto investor from 2017.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

December 2023 - present day Lavarage.

**Position**: Senior full stack developer. Tech Leader.

**Responsibilities**: Core developer of a Web3 project. Conducting indepth market analysis and conceptualizing business models. Smart contracts integration in the Solana network using Anchor. Design and implement user-friendly, convenient, intuitive and easy to understand UI. Collaborate with other team members, code review to write clean, efficient, and maintainable code while adhering to coding standards and best practices. Creating a modern landing page using Astro.

June 2023 - present day **Pine Protocol.** 

Components **Position**: Senior full stack developer.

**Responsibilities**: Core developer of Web3 project. Design and implement highly scalable, secure, and performant software architecture using NodeJS and ReactJS. Write clean, efficient, and maintainable code while adhering to coding standards and best practices. Collaborate with other team members, including marketing managers, product managers, and other developers. Stay up-to-date with the latest trends and technologies in the Web3 space, and apply them to our platform as appropriate. Participate in code reviews, testing, and debugging to ensure the quality and reliability of our platform. Creating analytical dashboards with Dune Analitiks.

After December 2023 - Product support only.

May 2023 - June 2023 Web Studio "Digital Freedom".

**Position**: Founder, team lead, full stack developer, product manager. **Responsibilities**: Managing a team of two front-end developers, two designers and one social media manager. Performing the role of devops and backend developer. solving more complex frontend tasks. Drafting technical specifications and working with clients.

December 2022 - May 2023 Web3 startup "Clandai".

**Position**: Frontend team lead, backend developer, product manager. **Responsibilities**: Development of a high-loaded backend for gaming platforms on nodeJS and express using PostgerSQL database (planned simultaneous online 10,000 players). Coordination of interaction between frontend, backend, web3 and game developers teams. Teamlead for frontend team. Development of tokenomics, whitepaper and main concepts of NFT and token utility.

#### **LANGUAGES**

- ▶ English Upper-Intermediate (B2)
- Ukrainian Native Speaker
- Russian Native Speaker

#### **SOFT SKILLS**

- Strong Communication
- Creative Problem Solving
- ▶ Effective Time Management
- Collaborative Team Player
- Adaptability and Flexibility
- Client Relationship Management
- Leadership and Motivation
- Stress Management
- Openness to new
- Logical thinking
- Emotion management
- Teamwork
- Attention to Detail

> 2012 - 2023 National Technical University of Ukraine "Igor Sikorsky Kyiv Polytechnic Institute".

Position: Senior Lecturer, Scientist.

**Responsibilities**: Teaching students, creating teaching materials and development of new technologies. Had experience in **programming microcontrollers** in low-level programming languages and application of **neural networks** approach. Development of adaptive vector control systems for asynchronous motors based on **artificial intelligence**.

**Development of algorithms** and complex of **programs** (based on **C++**) for modeling and experimental studying of adaptive vector control electro-mechanical complexes with an induction motor. The results are implemented in electromechanical traction systems for trolleybuses and tram cars of the State Enterprise "Research and Design Institute of Municipal Economy". Many of my scientific articles have been published in international journals.

2006 - 2023 **Sport club "Gran".** 

**Position**: Founder, PR, event organizer, main instructor, team leader. **Responsibilities**: Strategic planning of club development, communication with clients, organizations of B2B cooperation, SMM promotion, holding events, cooperation with instructors, client base management, automation of mailings in social networks and on e-mail.

#### **EDUCATION**

- 2004 2010 / National Technical University of Ukraine "Kyiv Polytechnic Institute", Faculty of Electrical Engineering and Automation, Department of Automation of Electromechanical Systems and Electric Drive / Master's degree in Electromechanics / Kyiv, Ukraine
- 2010 2016 / National Technical University of Ukraine "Kyiv Polytechnic Institute", Post-graduate course / PhD in Electrotechnical Complexes and Systems / Kyiv, Ukraine
- 2017 / Bitcoin and Cryptocurrency Technologies / Princeton University
- 2021 / Using advanced Google services for learning activities / NMC "Institute of Postgraduate Education"
- 2023 present day / Weekly English speaking club / Green Forest
- July 2024 September 2024 / Solana UA Bootcamp / Solana Foundation